

Hello 🤲 I'm Waris Radji

Computer Science Student & Freelancer

Age 20 years

France, Paris/Bordeaux Location

Phone +33 6 52 81 11 65

E-mail contact@warisradji.com https://warisradji.com Website

Interests Street Lifting, Competitive Programming, Biology

Versatile Developer fascinated by AI and procedural generation. I mainly worked in Scala but I can adapt to other languages while paying a lot of care to software design and performance. I have proven myself through my jobs and my open-source contributions and I am ready to take on new challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Centre Hospitalier Universitaire de Bordeaux

DATA ANALYST • Freelance

Prediction of drowning risk from daily Meteo France meteorological data and development of an associated dashboard and an alert system.





Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

Wellputt USA

LEAD KOTLIN DEVELOPER · Freelance

Development of an Android application to supervise golfers and decision making regarding the technical aspects of the project within the team.





Apr 2020 - Aug 2020

CNRS - Laboratoire d'Océanographie et du Climat

FULL-STACK DATA DEVELOPER • Internship

Development of new functionalities for L-SAT, a web platform for collaborative analysis and exploration of satellite data. Minor changes to existing data analysis codes.





Jul 2019 - Aug 2019

CNRS - Northern Paris Computer Science Lab

SCALA DATA DEVELOPER · Associate

Implementation of a bio-inspired and clustering algorithm (Ant-Tree) in Scala to integrate it into the Clustering4Ever library. Use of data visualization libraries and Apache Spark to write



EDUCATION

2020 - 2023



Engineer's degree in Computer Science - PhD track

ENSEIRB-MATMECA - Bordeaux Graduate School in Electronics, Computer Science, Telecommunications, Mathematics and Mechanics

Master the necessary fundamental, theoretical and practical aspects of the main fields of computer sciences in order to develop. I joined the PhD track, which prepares engineering students for scientific research and its applications, encourages R&D vocations and facilitates the understanding of doctoral studies, through seminars, round tables, visits, projects, specific modules, etc.

Probability Data Mining Formal Meth



https://github.com/riiswa 😱 https://www.instagram.com/riiswa/@

https://www.linkedin.com/in/warisr in

https://warisradji.com/ 🌐



Technical college degree in Computer Science

Université Sorbonne Paris Nord (DUT Informatique)

Multidisciplinary training that trains assistant engineers and project managers in management and industrial computing. Operational in software and hardware development, we have participated in the design, realization and implementation of computer systems.

OOP Database HCI Web Programming Agile Meth

2015 - 2018

High school diploma in Science & Mathematics

Lycée Camille-Saint-Saëns (Baccalauréat Scientifique)

Development of a real scientific culture based on knowledge and an experimental approach to science

***** ACHIEVEMENTS & PROJECTS

2021

Eirb'lA

CO-FOUNDER (with Hector Piteau)

Creation and management of the Artificial Intelligence club of **ENSEIRB-MATMECA** trough workshops, conferences, debates, competitions and paper popularization.

2021

Hackathon DefInSpace

LEAD TECH

24 hours to imagine solutions for space defense. My solution consisted in the implementation of a robust satellite network based on the Blockchain to ensure a reliable exchange of

2020-2021

Pokémon Workshop

LEAD BACK-END DEVELOPER

Creation of Pokémon Studio, a tool developed in React to create its Pokémon game project more simply. The goal is to replace Ruby Host, the Database editor, and to allow more relevance by leaving RPG Maker

2020

Scala Retro

CONTRIBUTOR

Development of a sbt plugin for Scala Retro, a package that allows to generate UML Class Diagrams from Scala source code

2020

Clustering4Ever

CONTRIBUTOR

Implement various algorithms into Clustering4Ever, a Big Data Clustering Library gathering clustering, unsupervised algorithms, and quality indices, written in Scala

2019

Hackathon Blockchain Margo X UNICEF

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

Develop in 48 hours a solution to record the key stages of the child's life on the Blockchain. I developed part of the Node.js back-end and wrote Solidity smart contracts to deploy them on the Ethereum Blockchain

2018

Ant Colony Simulator

MAIN DEVELOPER

Open source project about the simulation of an intelligent ant colony looking for the shortest path to a food source

SKILLS & KNOWLEDGE

♦ Scala Dotty, Scalameta, Cats, ZIO, Scalaz, Shapeless

👜 Data Science & ML Scikit-Learn, Spark MLLIB, Clustering4Ever, Smile, (No)SQL, NLTK

♦ Data Visualization D3.js, Plotly, ChartJS, Processing, Matplotlib, ggplot

Data/Cloud Engineering Apache Spark, Akka, Apache Kafka, Google Cloud Platform, Apache Lucene

Web Framework Play!, Flask, Django, Angular

Python, Java, JS/TS, Kotlin, C, MATLAB, Bash, C++, C#, R

□□ Language French ★★★★★, English ★★★, Spanish & Chinese ★